James Ciclitra

Product Designer based in London, creating complex digital products that lead to better user experiences. I love to design beautifully simple interfaces, code, iterate and create. I am an experienced and capable Digital Product Designer with over 2 years of professional experience.

EXPERIENCE

Product & Web development

Suggestv · January 2017 - April 2017

Suggestv is the inventor of semantic video distribution. I was responsible for designing and aiding in the production of a semantic video distribution platform using React.

Product designer

CrowdScores · September 2015 - January 2017

CrowdScores is a real-time sports data application. I had the pleasure of working as the principal designer taking responsibility for a variety of roles. Responsible included improving the existing product, developing new features research, conceptualising ideas & prototyping.

Freelance designer

Prediction labs · January 2017 - Present

Numilli app - Bitcoin safe and easy. Numilli aims to makes it easy to securely buy and sell bitcoin currency, on the go using a mobile app & ATM machine.

Freelance designer

Foreminds • March 2017 - Present

BaseSight - workforce management platform, which aims to help improve efficiency & productivity

EDUCATION

Edinburgh College Of Art • 2011 - 2015

Product Design - 2:1 ba (Hons)

DESIGN SKILLS

Sketching Grid & Layout

UI/UX Design Color Theory

Interaction Design Typography

DESIGN TOOLS











